Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Deans George Blumer, Milton C. Winternitz, Stanhope Bayne-Jones, Francis G. Blake, and Cyril N. H. Long, 1888-1960; Accession 1961-A-002
  - Departmental Correspondence
    - Primate Biology, Yale Laboratories of, 1936-1951 (Box 37, Folder 616 - 621)
      - Abstract of Material in Advisory Committee Folder, President's file, 1924-1937 (Box 37, Folder 622)
      - Abstract of Material in Anthropoid Breeding Station folder, President's file and Yerkes correspondence, 1929-1937 (Box 38, Folder 623)
      - Administrative Committee, 1938-1941 (Box 38, Folder 624 - 628)
      - Administrative Committee and Reorganization, 1941 September 1942 - June (Box 38, Folder 629)
      - Annual Report, Eight, 1936-1937 (Box 38, Folder 630)
      - Annual Report, Ninth, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 631)
      - Allowance for Committee Expenses, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 632)
      - Budget and Personnel, 1931-1942 (Box 38, Folder 633 - 636)
      - By-laws, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 637)
      - Charter - Incorporation, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 638)
      - Committee on Apraisal and Recommendation, Report of, 1935 August (Box 39, Folder 639)
      - Consultants (outside investigators), 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 640)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1936-1940 (Box 39, Folder 641)
      - Fels Fund - Infant Behavior Research, 1939-1942 (Box 39, Folder 642)
      - Memoranda and Reports relative to Department and Laboratories, clippings and notes, 1928-1939 (Box 39, Folder 643)
      - Minutes of Committee Meetings, 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 644)
      - Orange Park - Boiler Explosion Insurance, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 645)
      - Physiology Building at Orange Park, 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 646)
      - President Charles Seymour, 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 647)
      - Reorganization, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 648)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 649)
      - Rockefeller Foundation - Dr. Warren Weaver, 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 650)
      - Scientific Advisory Board, 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 651)
      - Special Committee (Drs. Allen, Fulton, Miles, S. Bayne-Jones, Provost Furniss), 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 652)
      - Scientific Advisory Goard - Meeting of 22-1923 March, 1937, in Orange Park, Florida, 1936-1937 (Box 40, Folder 653)
      - Votes of Yale Corporation and Incorporators, 1939-1940 (Box 40, Folder 654)
    - Primate Biology, Yerkes Laboratory of, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 655)
    - Primate Biology, Yerkes Laboratory of, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 40, Folder 656 - 658)
    - Psychiatric Clinic, 1931-1944 (Box 40, Folder 659 - 660)
    - Psychiatry, 1915-1926 (Box 40, Folder 661 - 665)
    - Psychiatry, Department of, 1942-1959 (Box 40, Folder 666)
    - Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, Department of, 1918-1941 (Box 40, Folder 667 - 670)
    - Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, Department of, 1929-1947 (Box 41, Folder 671 - 692)
    - Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, Department of, 1947-1951 (Box 42, Folder 693 - 694)
      - Drug Addict Clinic, 1939-1942 (Box 42, Folder 695)
      - Physiological Psychology, Laboratory of Miles, 1930-1938 (Box 42, Folder 696 - 697)
    - Psychobiology See also: Yerkes, Prof. Robert M. Primate Biology, 1929-1936 (Box 42, Folder 698 - 699)
      - Sterling Hall of Medicine Extension See also: Primate Biology, 1930-1931 (Box 42, Folder 700)
    - Psychology, Department of, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 701)
      - Decompression Sickness, Dr. Fulton, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 702)
    - Public Health, 1916-1920 (Box 42, Folder 703)
      - Association of Schools of, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 704)
      - Civil Affairs Training Program, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 705)
      - Committee on, 1932-1939 (Box 42, Folder 706 - 709)
      - Committee on Development of Department, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 710)
    - Public Health, Department of, 1923-1947 (Box 42, Folder 711 - 714)
    - Public Health, Department of, 1935-1952 (Box 43, Folder 715 - 725)
      - Budgets, 1920-1937 (Box 43, Folder 726)
      - Course in Industrial Health and Medicine in War Time, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 727)
      - Distict Health Unit, 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 728)
      - Reports, 1923-1934 (Box 44, Folder 729)
      - Students, 1928-1946 (Box 44, Folder 730 - 732)
      - U.S. Public Health Postgraduate Course, undated (Box 44, Folder 733)
    - Public Health Service, United States, 1922-1923 (Box 44, Folder 734)
      - Questions on Demography, 1914 (Box 44, Folder 735)
      - Questionnaires, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 736)
    - Radiology, Chair in, 1932-1933 (Box 44, Folder 737)
    - Radiology, Department of, 1919-1948 (Box 44, Folder 738 - 740)
      - Radioisotopes, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 741)
      - X-ray, Special Account, 1934-1947 (Box 44, Folder 742)
    - Radiology, Section of, 1941-1946 (Box 44, Folder 743)
    - Stock Room, 1933 February-December (Box 44, Folder 744)
    - Surgery, Department of, 1916-1952 (Box 45, Folder 745 - 753)
      - Tumor Clinic, 1931-1939 (Box 45, Folder 754)
      - Section of Urology, 1939-1946 (Box 45, Folder 755)
    - Surgical-Bacteriological Laboratory, 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 756)
    - Surgical-Pathological Laboratory, 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 757)
    - University Health, Department of, 1920-1938 (Box 45, Folder 758 - 761)
      - Psychiatric Service - Students, 1935-1939 (Box 45, Folder 762)
  - Dormitory, 1948-1952 (Box 45, Folder 763 - 766)
    - Correspondence, general, 1929-1942 (Box 46, Folder 767 - 770)
    - Equipment, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 771)
    - Facilities, 1945-1948 (Box 46, Folder 772 - 774)
  - Duplicates of Correspondence - Winternitz, Angell, 1920-1928 (Box 46, Folder 775)
  - Electrocardiography, 1918-19 (Box 46, Folder 776)
  - Equipment, 1949-1950 (Box 46, Folder 777)
  - Examinations, 1933-1947 (Box 46, Folder 778 - 781)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1949 (Box 47, Folder 782 - 784)
    - Grades, 1927-1949 (Box 47, Folder 785 - 789)
    - Clinical, 1932-1941 (Box 47, Folder 790)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1926-1947 (Box 47, Folder 791 - 794)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1926-1943 (Box 48, Folder 795 - 807)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1944-1951 (Box 49, Folder 808 - 815)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1937-1952 (Box 50, Folder 816 - 821)
    - Ph.D. Qualifying Examination, 1933-1942 (Box 50, Folder 822)
    - Preclinical, 1927-1942 (Box 50, Folder 823)
    - Schedules, 1896-1927 (Box 50, Folder 824)
  - Examining Rooms, 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 825)
    - Correspondence, Regulations, etc., 1938-1940 (Box 50, Folder 826)
  - Experiments, undated (Box 50, Folder 827 - 828)
  - Extension, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 829)
  - Extra Diagrams, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 830)
  - Faculty By-Laws, 1909-18 (Box 51, Folder 831)
  - Faculty Women's Guild, 1938-1943 (Box 51, Folder 832)
  - Faculty Work Sheets, 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 833)
  - Federal Support of Research, 1945-1946 (Box 51, Folder 834 - 835)
    - University Committee on, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 836)
  - Financial Records, General
    - Accounts, 1940-1941 (Box 51, Folder 837)
    - Aesculapian Frolic, 1941-1942 (Box 51, Folder 838)
    - Allen, Edgar - Partrait Fund, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 840)
    - Alumni Fund, 1916-1925 (Box 51, Folder 841)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (permanent Science Fund) Grant to A. White and K.G. Stern, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 842)
    - American Medical Association (committee on Therapeutic Research, Council of Pharmacy and Chemistry) Grant, 1935-1936 (Box 51, Folder 843)
    - Applications for Grants, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 844)
    - Artist Account, 1935-1936 (Box 51, Folder 845)
    - Babbit, Frank L. Fund, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 846)
    - Beeson's office, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 847)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1936-1940 (Box 51, Folder 848 - 849)
    - Benefactors, 1925-1932 (Box 51, Folder 850)
    - Bennett Maintenance Fund for Dispensary Endowment, 1910 (Box 51, Folder 851)
    - Blake, F. G. - Chicago offer, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 852)
    - Book store, Medical, 1942-1946 (Box 51, Folder 853 - 854)
    - Brady Memorial Lab, 1919-1931 (Box 51, Folder 855)
    - Brainard, C.S. - Endowment, 1913 (Box 51, Folder 856)
    - Bronson Professorship of Comparative Anatomy, 1939 (Box 52)
    - Browning, Henry, 1950-1951 (Box 52)
    - Budgets, correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1915-1949 (Box 52)
    - Calhoun, Edward Thomas - Fund - Pathology, 1928 (Box 52)
    - Campbell, James Prize, 1942-1944 (Box 52)
    - Cardiovascular Training Grant, 1952-1953 (Box 52)
    - Carmalt, William H. - Bequest - Beaumont Lectureship, 1930 (Box 52)
    - CarrGalt, William H. - Professorhip, Surgery, 1924 (Box 52)
    - Child Welfare Re·search Fund, 1940-1941 (Box 52)
      - Pediatrics, 1940-1941 (Box 52)
    - Chittenden, Russell H. Fund, 1915 (Box 52)
    - Clinical Charges, 1931-1935 (Box 52)
    - Clinical facilities, the development of Memorandum, 1928 (Box 52)
    - Clinical Research and Teaching Fund, 1935-1940 (Box 52)
    - Clinical Research and Teaching Fund, 1935-1944 (Box 53)
    - Coffin Childs Fund - (Jane Coffin Childs Memorial Fund for Medical Research), 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 857)
      - Apparatus for Physiological Chemical Researches - Project 16 (Stern, K.G.), 1938 (Box 53, Folder 858)
      - Burr, 1937-1938 (Box 53, Folder 859)
      - Project 18-: Tennant, R.A., 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 860)
      - Tumor Clinic - Project 23C, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 861)
      - Project 17 - Winternitz, 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 862)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 863)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1949-1950 (Box 53, Folder 864)
    - Coxe, A.B. Fellowship, 1927-1946 (Box 53, Folder 865 - 866)
    - Coxe, A. B. Project: Gutman, H.R., Hoberman, 1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 867)
    - Davis and Geck Fund: Surgery, 1930-1937 (Box 53, Folder 870)
    - Dazian Foundation, 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 871)
    - Dean's Fund, 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 872)
    - Deaths and Bequests (national, not Yale), 1931-1935 (Box 53, Folder 873)
    - Donnelley, Ruben H. Scholarship Fund, 1940-1944 (Box 53, Folder 874)
    - Dormitories, 1940-1942 (Box 53, Folder 875)
    - Employees, non-faculty, payment of, 1951-1952 (Box 53, Folder 876)
    - Enders, Thomas B. Fund: Internal Medicine, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 877)
    - Expense Account Book: Medical Department, 1912-1916 (Box 53, Folder 879)
    - Fellowships: general information, 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 880)
    - Ferris, Harry Burr
      - Lectureship in Anatomy, 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 881)
      - Memorial Fund, 1941-1945 (Box 53, Folder 882)
      - Prize in Anatomy, 1933-1938 (Box 53, Folder 883 - 885)
    - Filene, Edward A., 1935 (Box 53, Folder 886)
    - Financial Aid: Emergency, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 887)
    - Finney-Howell Research Foundation, Inc., 1939 (Box 53, Folder 888)
    - Fitkin, Abram E. Fund, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 889)
    - Forbes, T.R., 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 890)
    - Fuller Fund, The Anna, 1930-1935 (Box 54, Folder 893)
    - Funds and Foundations, 1930-1947 (Box 56, Folder 913 - 914)
    - General Hospital Society of Connecticut, 1936-1938 (Box 56, Folder 915)
    - Grace-New Haven Hospital, 1946-1950 (Box 56, Folder 916)
    - Gifts, 1931-1940 (Box 56, Folder 917 - 918)
      - Treasurer's office, 1949-1950 (Box 56, Folder 919)
    - Gifts and Grants, 1937-1939 (Box 56, Folder 920 - 923)
    - Goodrich Scholarships, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 924)
    - Haemolytic Streptococci Research Project, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 925)
    - Harriman Fund for Orthodedics, 1917-1936 (Box 56, Folder 926)
    - Hospital Fund, New Haven
      - Doctors' committee, 1929-1931 (Box 56, Folder 927)
      - Invitation list to become founders, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 928)
      - Plan of Campaign, 1929-1930 (Box 56, Folder 929)
      - Special Gifts Committee, 1931-1932 (Box 56, Folder 930 - 931)
        - Luncheon, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 932)
    - House Staff Payroll, 1949-1952 (Box 57, Folder 933 - 936)
    - Human Welfare Endowment Fund, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 942)
    - Human Welfare Group, 1929-1931 (Box 57, Folder 943)
      - Walter B. James Memorial, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 944)
    - Income: Ensign Professorship (Medicine), 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 945)
    - Income and Expen.se·, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 946)
    - India Tea Bureau, The, 1936-1937 (Box 57, Folder 947)
    - International Cancer Research Foundation, 1939-1944 (Box 57, Folder 948)
    - Ives, Bessie W. Scholarship, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 949)
    - Kellogg, W.K. Foundation: correspondence, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 950)
    - Kellogg, W.K. Foundation Grant: Public Health, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 951)
    - Lapman Memorial Fund, 1939-1948 (Box 57, Folder 952)
    - Markle, JOhn and Mary R. Foundation, 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 953)
      - Grant: Stone, L.S., Anatomy, 1938-1946 (Box 58, Folder 954)
    - Memoranda, 1950-1952 (Box 58, Folder 955)
    - Memorial Gifts, 1929 (Box 58, Folder 956)
    - Mendelsohn Fund, 1919 (Box 58, Folder 957)
    - Metabolish Fund: Internal Medicine, 1930-1931 (Box 58, Folder 958)
    - Meyer, Eugene III Gift, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 959)
    - National Research Council: Committee for Research in Problems of Sex, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 960)
    - New Haven Hospital, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 961)
    - Nutrition Foundation, Inc., 1942-1944 (Box 58, Folder 962)
    - Nutrition, Journal of Fund (CdWgil1), 1941-1944 (Box 58, Folder 963)
    - Pathology: Dr. Satoru VTatanabe, 1950-1951 (Box 58, Folder 964)
    - Pediatrics: Dr. Mary O. Godenne, 1950-1951 (Box 58, Folder 965)
    - Pension Plans: Employees Social Security, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 966)
    - Petty Cash, 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 967)
    - Pharmacology, Laboratory of: Grants, Applications for, 1936-1937 (Box 58, Folder 968)
    - Physiological Sciences, Department of, 1921-1932 (Box 58, Folder 969 - 970)
    - Plotz, Ella Sach Foundation: Internal Medicine, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 971)
    - Polio: anonymous gift, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 972)
    - Projects, General: pending, 1927-1931 (Box 58, Folder 973)
    - Psychiatry
      - Denison Request, 1939-1945 (Box 58, Folder 974)
      - Reserve for furnishings, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 975)
    - Proposal for 500 dollars in Perpetuity, 1930 (Box 58, Folder 976)
    - Public Health:-Special Scho1rship Fund, 1938-194 (Box 58, Folder 977 - 978)
    - Rackham Ftmd, The Horace H. and Mary A., 1934 (Box 59, Folder 980)
    - Ramsy, Otto G. Fund, 1915 (Box 59, Folder 981)
    - Receipts: student accounts, 1932-1937 (Box 59, Folder 982)
    - Financial Records, General (cont'd.), 1938-1940 (Box 59, Folder 983)
    - Reckford Bequest, 1937-1945 (Box 59, Folder 984)
    - Recreational Unit: Grants, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 985)
    - Requisitions, 1926-1948 (Box 59, Folder 986)
    - Research and Clinical Fellows, 1930-1948 (Box 59, Folder 987 - 988)
    - Research Fellows, 1928-1933 (Box 59, Folder 989 - 990)
    - Research Funds: Requests for Research Grants, 1930-1938 (Box 59, Folder 994)
      - Pathology, 1930-1938 (Box 59, Folder 995)
      - Pediatrics, 1930-1938 (Box 59, Folder 996)
      - Pharmacology and Toxicology, 1930-1938 (Box 59, Folder 997)
      - Physiological Chemistry, 1930-1938 (Box 59, Folder 998)
      - Physiology, 1934-1936 (Box 59, Folder 999)
      - Psychiatry and 1·1enta1 Hygiene, 1933~35 (Box 59, Folder 1000)
      - Psychobiology, 1931-1937 (Box 59, Folder 1001)
      - Surgery, 1930 (Box 60, Folder 1002)
    - Rockford Research Fund, 1926-1941 (Box 60, Folder 1004)
    - Rosenwald, Julius Fund, 1930-1935 (Box 60, Folder 1005)
    - Salmon, Thomas W. Memorial Inc., 1941-1943 (Box 60, Folder 1006)
    - Scholarships, gifts_ and source, 1941-1942 (Box 60, Folder 1007)
    - Scholarships, special, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 1008)
    - Statistics, 1908-1951 (Box 60, Folder 1009)
    - Stoeckel, Robbins Battell - Nursing gift, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 1010)
    - Stokes to Blumer - re: fund raising, 1919 (Box 60, Folder 1011)
    - Students' Loan Fund of Yale Men in Medicine, Incorporated, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 1012)
    - Subscriptions, acknowledgements of, 1931-1932 (Box 60, Folder 1013)
    - Swift and Comapnx - Grants-in-Aid to Universities, 1943 (Box 60, Folder 1014)
    - Thomas, Charles Henry Memorial Scholarship, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 1015)
    - Treasurer's office, 1941-1953 (Box 60, Folder 1016)
      - Budget, 1949-1950 (Box 60, Folder 1017)
      - Budger and general, 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 1018)
      - Contracts, 1949-1950 (Box 60, Folder 1019)
      - Gifts and Grants, 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 1021)
      - Twentieth Century and Good Will Funds, 1939 (Box 60, Folder 1022)
      - Winternitz, M. C., 1923-1938 (Box 60, Folder 1023)
  - Financial Records - Budgets
    - Departmental Budgets
      - Anatomy, 1919-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1024)
      - Bacteriology, 1934-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1025)
      - Child Study Center, 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1026)
      - Clinic of Child Development, 1936-1948 (Box 61, Folder 1027)
      - Dispensary, 1928-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1028)
      - Examining Rooms, 1947-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1029)
      - Furniture and Equipment, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 1030)
      - Grace-New Haven Community Hospital, 1949-1951 (Box 61, Folder 1031)
      - Immunology, 1933-1942 (Box 61, Folder 1032)
      - Institute of Occupational Medicine and Hygiene, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 1033)
      - Internal Medicine, 1934-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1034)
      - Media, 1928-1931 (Box 61, Folder 1035)
      - Neurophysiology, 1935-1942 (Box 61, Folder 1036)
      - New Haven Hospital - Amount of School of Medicine departmental budgets expended for clinical services, 1935-1945 (Box 61, Folder 1037)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1940-1948 (Box 61, Folder 1038)
      - Pathology, 1947-1951 (Box 61, Folder 1039)
      - Pediatrics, 1940-1948 (Box 61, Folder 1040)
      - Pharmacology, 1940-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1041)
      - Photography, 1928-1934 (Box 61, Folder 1042)
      - Physiological Chemistry, 1940-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1043)
      - Physiology Department, undated (Box 61, Folder 1044)
      - Physiology, 1937-1944 (Box 61, Folder 1045)
      - Preventative Medicine, 1940-1945 (Box 61, Folder 1046)
      - Primate Biology, 1937-1942 (Box 61, Folder 1047)
      - Proto Biology, 1928-1931 (Box 61, Folder 1048)
      - Psychiatric Clinic, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1049)
      - Psychiatry, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1050)
      - Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, 1935-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1051)
      - Public Health, 1939-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1052)
      - Radiology, 1946-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1053)
      - Radiology-Appointments, 1925-1943 (Box 62, Folder 1054)
      - Surgery, 1920-1949 (Box 62, Folder 1055 - 1057)
    - Medical School Administration, 1910-1920 (Box 62, Folder 1058 - 1067)
    - Moving to Nathan Smith, etc., 1918-19 (Box 62, Folder 1068)
    - Nathan Smith Hall and other Park Street Property, 1919-1920 (Box 62, Folder 1069)
    - Medical School Budgets, 1908-1921 (Box 62, Folder 1070 - 1071)
    - Medical School Budget Estimates, 1919 October (Box 62, Folder 1072)
    - Medical School Budgets, 1920-1952 (Box 63, Folder 1073 - 1090)
    - Medical School Budgets, 1934-1945 (Box 64, Folder 1091 - 1101)
    - Medical School Budgets, 1945-1953 (Box 65, Folder 1102 - 1110)
      - Letters, 1935-1937 (Box 65, Folder 1111)
      - Letters 1-10, 1932-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1112)
      - Letters 11-1920, 1932-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1113)
      - Material, General, 1929-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1114 - 1122)
      - Material, General, 1946-1952 (Box 67, Folder 1123 - 1129)
      - Statistics and Budgets, General, 1931-1936 (Box 67, Folder 1130)
  - Financial Records - Fluid Research Fund, 1930-1944 (Box 70, Folder 1195 - 1202)
  - Financial Records - Fluid Research Fund, 1945-1947 (Box 71, Folder 1203 - 1204)
    - Aberle, S.B. and Watkins, J.H., 1935-1938 (Box 71, Folder 1205)
    - Awards, 1938-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1206)
    - Barron, D.H., 1943-1946 (Box 71, Folder 1207)
    - Barron, undated (Box 71, Folder 1208)
    - Bayne-Jones, 1942 (Box 71, Folder 1209)
    - Blake, F.G., 1933-1940 (Box 71, Folder 1210)
    - Blake, F.G. and Crocker, T.T., 1948-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1211)
    - Blake, F.G. and Tamm, I., 1949 (Box 71, Folder 1212)
    - Blake, Howard and Tatlock, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 1213)
    - Brody, B.S. and Gilman, A.Z:, 1935-1931 (Box 71, Folder 1214)
    - Bruhn, M., 1933-1931 (Box 71, Folder 1215)
    - Burn, e.G., 1930-1931 (Box 71, Folder 1216)
    - Committee, 1941-1946 (Box 71, Folder 1217)
    - Cowgill, G.R., 1946 (Box 71, Folder 1218)
    - Cowles, Philip B., 1939-1940 (Box 71, Folder 1219)
    - Danowski, T.S., 1945-1946 (Box 71, Folder 1220)
    - Darrow, D.C. and Miller, R.C., 1935-1936 (Box 71, Folder 1221)
    - Deming, C.L., 1944-1945 (Box 71, Folder 1222)
    - Departments
      - Anatomy, 1921-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1223 - 1226)
        - Allan, E., 1933-1942 (Box 71, Folder 1227)
        - Burr, H.S., 1933-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1228)
        - Forbes, T.R., 1945-1947 (Box 71, Folder 1229)
        - Gardner, W.V., 1932-1950 (Box 71, Folder 1230)
        - Hill, R.T., 1935-1937 (Box 71, Folder 1231)
        - Knight Fund, 1930-1938 (Box 72, Folder 1232)
        - Stone, L.S., 1933-1948 (Box 72, Folder 1233 - 1234)
      - Bacteriology
        - Briody, B.A., 1948-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1235)
        - Haley, L.D., 1950-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1236)
        - Rettger, 1930 (Box 72, Folder 1237)
        - Sladgley, E.W., 1944-1949 (Box 72, Folder 1238)
        - Smith. G.H. - Barnett, R., 1947-1949 (Box 72, Folder 1239)
        - Tager, M., 1945-1947 (Box 72, Folder 1240)
      - Cardiovascular Study Unit, 1950-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1241)
      - Child Study Department: Gessel, A., 1942-1943 (Box 72, Folder 1242)
      - Immunology, 1931-1932 (Box 72, Folder 1243)
        - Cowles, P.B., 1940-1943 (Box 72, Folder 1244)
        - Lindsay, M.K., 1932-1934 (Box 72, Folder 1245)
      - Internal Medicine, 1946-1947 (Box 72, Folder 1246)
        - Engstrom, W. W., 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1247)
        - Erslev, A., 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1248)
        - Geiger, A.J., 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1249)
        - Goodyear, A.V.N., 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1250)
        - Klatskin, G., 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1251)
        - Man, E.B., 1950-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1252)
        - Peters, J.P., 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1253)
        - Seldin, D.W., 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1254)
        - Sims, E.A.H., 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1255)
        - Van Eck, 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1256)
      - Microbiology
        - Briody, B.A., 1950-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1257)
        - Tref'fers, 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1258)
        - Treffers-Gelperin, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 1259)
      - Neurology
        - Cushing, H., 1935-1938 (Box 72, Folder 1260)
        - Miles, W.R., 1939-1940 (Box 72, Folder 1261)
      - Nutrition
        - Cowgill, G.R., 1930-1947 (Box 72, Folder 1262)
        - Fenton, P.F., 1948-1949 (Box 72, Folder 1263)
        - Obstetrics: Greulich, W.W., 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 1264)
        - Obstetrics-Gynecology: Thoms, 1951-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1265)
        - Otoaryngology: Canfield, N., 1935-1942 (Box 72, Folder 1266)
      - Pathology
        - Barnett, R.N., 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1267)
        - Greene, H.N.S., 1948-1949 (Box 72, Folder 1268)
        - Hussey, R., 1930-1937 (Box 72, Folder 1269)
      - Pediatrics
        - Boisvert, P.L., 1943-1948 (Box 72, Folder 1270 - 1271)
        - Clement, D.H., 1947-1948 (Box 72, Folder 1272)
        - Culotta~ C.S~, 1936-1939 (Box 72, Folder 1273)
        - Darrow, 'D. C~ -, 1949-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1274)
        - Dunham, E.,C., 1933-1938 (Box 72, Folder 1275)
        - Johnson, R.D., 1942 (Box 72, Folder 1276)
        - Kempe, C.H. and Olmsted, R.W., 1949 (Box 72, Folder 1277)